<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AlfahrelRifananda</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AlfahrelRifananda</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© AlfahrelRifananda</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:15:00 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Create a free custom VPN toggle script for Waybar</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Managing VPN connections on Linux shouldn&amp;rsquo;t require opening terminals and typing commands. After getting tired of manually starting and stopping OpenVPN services, I built a custom toggle script for Waybar that does it all with a single click. Here&amp;rsquo;s how it works and how you can build your own.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re using a tiling window manager with Waybar, you probably appreciate quick access to system controls. But VPN management often gets left out—you end up with some clunky system tray app or resort to terminal commands. I wanted something better: a clean status indicator in my bar, one-click toggling, and random server selection for better privacy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why React is Ruining the Web</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:45:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;React has become the default choice for web development, but at what cost? Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about how the React ecosystem has led us down a path of unnecessary complexity, bloated bundles, and websites that fail basic usability standards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I need to start with a confession: I&amp;rsquo;ve built dozens of production applications with React. I understand its appeal. The component model is elegant, the ecosystem is vast, and the developer experience can be quite nice. But somewhere along the way, we stopped asking whether we should use React and started assuming we must use it for everything.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Hugo is the Best Static Site Generator</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:30:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After years of wrestling with slow build times, complicated setups, and bloated frameworks, I discovered Hugo. Here&amp;rsquo;s why it stands head and shoulders above the rest.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re building websites in 2026, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard of static site generators. There are dozens of options out there—Jekyll, Gatsby, Next.js, Eleventy, and many more. Each has its strengths, but after trying them all, I keep coming back to Hugo. Not out of habit, but because it genuinely solves problems that other generators simply can&amp;rsquo;t match.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me - Alfahrel Rifananda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hi, my name is &lt;strong&gt;Nabillio Alfahrel Rifananda.&lt;/strong&gt; You can call me &lt;em&gt;Fahrel.&lt;/em&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m a fresh graduate from &lt;strong&gt;Vocational High School 5 Surakarta&lt;/strong&gt; with a major in &lt;strong&gt;Software Engineering.&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m currently 20 years old and actively looking for a job.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;life&#34;&gt;Life&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was born on &lt;strong&gt;March 3rd, 2005 in Solo, Indonesia.&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ve lived my entire life in this city, and it holds a special place in my heart. Everything about Solo is just wonderful. I currently live with my grandmother. My parents separated when I was young, and custody was given to my mother. However, we don&amp;rsquo;t live under the same roof because the house isn&amp;rsquo;t large enough, so she had to move to a kost (small apartment) with my older brother. Despite this, she visits me regularly and provides financial support every week. I rarely see my father—the last time was about a year ago. I&amp;rsquo;m uncertain about his current whereabouts or situation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
